drjays.com 2004-04-09

# DrJays.com

  |    
**Privacy Policy **

The Internet is a powerful tool allowing its users to exchange information freely. As a recipient of information collected on **DrJays.com** (the "Site"), **Dr. Jay's** ("we", "our" or "us") have policies about how we use the information we collect.

**Categories of Information**  
Information about you can be categorized as (a) personally identifiable information or (b) non-personally identifiable information. "Personally identifiable information" is information that we collect from you such as your name, postal address, telephone number, fax number and email address. "Non-personally identifiable information" is information that we collect from you that cannot be used to identify or contact you, such as your Web site browsing patterns or demographic information.

**How We Use and Disclose Information**  
We will use your personally identifiable information for customer service, such as to fulfill your orders, to provide you with information that you may request, to give you updates about the status of your orders, to notify you if you have won a prize and to customize your experience on the Site. We may also combine the information we have gathered about you with information from other sources, such as other Web sites operated by us, to better serve your needs. Unless you tell us not to, we may use your personally identifiable information to contact you about offers or promotions we think you would be interested in. If you do not want to receive this information, indicate that we may not do so at the point where you give us your personally identifiable information. If you change your mind later, email us at [_optout@DrJays.com_](mailto:optout@DrJays.com?subject=Remove). Email messages will also provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of receiving this information. Please note that changes to your preferences may not be effective immediately.

It is important for you to understand that we use third party contractors to help us operate our business, such as operating the server for the Site, performing delivery and shipping services, and sending postal mail and email, and may share your information with these contractors for those limited purposes. We generally require that contractors do not disclose personally identifiable information or use it other than as necessary to perform services for us.

Because we care about your privacy, we will not give your personally identifiable information to third parties, such as marketers or retailers, for them to use to contact you about offers or promotions of their own (other than, of course, in connection with the sale of our business), unless you allow us to. If you would like us to share your personally identifiable information with third parties so that you may receive these special offers and promotions, indicate that we may do so at the point where you give us such personally identifiable information. Please note that changes to your preferences may not be effective immediately.

In the event that all of our business assets are transferred to or acquired by another company, customer information will be one of the transferred assets. We will divulge your personal information to law enforcement officials if required to do so by law.

**How We Collect Information**  
We will collect personally identifiable information from you when you actively give us the information. Examples of this may include when you order products, register for gifts, fill out online site registration forms, enter contests or sweepstakes, request that we send you information, newsletters or catalogs, participate in community features, or respond to our surveys or other requests for visitor responses. All information we collect about you resides on servers owned and operated by New Media Merchants, Inc., a third party service provider.

Like many other commercial Web sites, we collect non-personally identifiable information from you by "passive" means, in other words by tracking your use of the Site, often through the use of cookies. That information includes, among other things, the type of computer operating system and net browser that are being used and the domain name of your Internet service provider, as well as some of the information described below. We use this information for internal purposes and to help us interact with visitors to the Site. We may also share this information in the aggregate form with third parties to illustrate trends and patterns.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small data file that is placed on your computer's hard drive that may contain information (such as a unique user ID) that a Web site may use to track certain things. We use cookies in order to improve your shopping experience. The cookie helps us track the pages of the Site that you visit, tells us whether you have been to the Site before and tells us which Web site you visited immediately before visiting the Site, but does not tell us about your use of any other Web sites. Sometimes advertisers and other third parties on the Site may also use cookies. You can keep us from using cookies by turning them off in your browser. However, if you turn off your cookies then you will not be enabled to make purchases from the Site or to access your account information.

**Special Policies for Children Identifying Themselves as Under Age 13**  
This Site is not intended for use by children. We will not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information submitted by visitors to the Site who are under the age of 13.

**Links**  
The Site contains links to other sites, including, among others, those of advertisers, other third parties and companies whose trademarks may appear on the Site. Sometimes promotions, contests or sweepstakes advertised on the Site might be sponsored by third parties. The other sites and third parties maintain their own privacy policies that may be different from ours. Visitors using such links or pursuing or entering such contests or sweepstakes should consult the privacy notices associated with those links, promotions, contests or sweepstakes. We do not control this collection of information and are not responsible or liable for the privacy policies maintained or actions taken by third parties with regard to your information. Our Privacy Policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, and therefore beyond our control. Please keep in mind that whenever you give out personal information online-for example, via message boards or chat rooms-that information can be collected, intercepted and used by people you do not know. You should use such community functions at your own risk.

**Security**  
Protecting your order information is important to us. Our third party service provider, New Media Merchants, Inc., uses the industry standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect the security of your online order information. SSL encryption is a method by which information is encrypted while being transmitted over the Internet. To check the security of your connection, look at the lower left-hand corner of your browser window after accessing the server. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending on your browser), then SSL is active. You can also double-check by looking at the URL line of your browser. When accessing a secure server, the first characters of the Site address should change from "http" to "https." Some versions of browsers and some firewalls don't permit communication through secure servers. In that case, you won't be able to connect to the server and therefore won't be able to place an order through an insecure connection. While no method is completely impenetrable, SSL is the state-of-the-art encryption technology used in E-Commerce today. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we are committed to protecting your personally identifiable information, we along with our third party provider(s) cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us.

**Your Acceptance of These Terms**  
By using the Site, you indicate your agreement with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, then do not use the Site. We reserve the right to change the terms of this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Site following any changes to this Privacy Policy will be deemed to constitute your acceptance of such changes. Please check this page regularly for any changes.

**Contact Us**  
Please contact us with any questions or comments regarding our privacy policy:  

> Phone Number: 1-888-4-DrJays  
>  Email: [_service@DrJays.com_](mailto:service@DrJays.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy)

|   |
